<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aesops Fables</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_lionin_love">The Lion in Love</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_ass_brains">The Ass Brains</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_old_woman_and_the_wine_jar">The Old Woman and the Wine Jar</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_miserand_his_gold">The Miser and His Gold</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_doginthe_manger">The Dog in the Manger</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_old_manand_death">The Old Man and Death</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_bald_manandthe_fly">The Bald Man and the Fly</string>
    <string name="title_activity_herculesandthe_waggoner">Hercules and the Waggoner</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_manand_his_two_wives">The Man and His Two Wives</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_labourerandthe_nightingale">The Labourer and the Nightingale
    </string>
    <string name="fable_1_text">A Lion once fell in love with a beautiful maiden and proposed marriage to her parents.\n\n

The old people did not know what to say.\n \n

They did not like to give their daughter to the Lion, yet they did not wish to enrage the King of Beasts.\n \n

At last the father said:\n \n

"We feel highly honoured by your Majesty's proposal, but you see our daughter is a tender young thing, and we fear that in the vehemence of your affection you might possibly do her some injury. Might I venture to suggest that your Majesty should have your claws removed, and your teeth extracted, then we would gladly consider your proposal again."\n \n

The Lion was so much in love that he had his claws trimmed and his big teeth taken out.\n \n

But when he came again to the parents of the young girl they simply laughed in his face, and bade him do his worst.</string>

    <string name="fable_2_text">The Lion and the Fox went hunting together. \n \n

The Lion, on the advice of the Fox, sent a message to the Ass, proposing to make an alliance between their two families. \n \n

The Ass came to the place of meeting, overjoyed at the prospect of a royal alliance. \n \n

But when he came there the Lion simply pounced on the Ass, and said to the Fox: \n \n

"Here is our dinner for to-day. Watch you here while I go and have a nap. Woe betide you if you touch my prey."

The Lion went away and the Fox waited; but finding that his master did not return, ventured to take out the brains of the Ass and ate them up.

When the Lion came back he soon noticed the absence of the brains, and asked the Fox in a terrible voice: \n \n

"What have you done with the brains?" \n \n

"Brains, your Majesty! it had none, or it would never have fallen into your trap." \n \n

 </string>

    <string name="fable_3_text">You must know that sometimes old women like a glass of wine. \n \n

One of this sort once found a Wine-jar lying in the road, and eagerly went up to it hoping to find it full. \n \n

But when she took it up she found that all the wine had been drunk out of it. \n \n

Still she took a long sniff at the mouth of the Jar. \n \n

"Ah," she cried: "What memories cling 'round the instruments of our pleasure."</string>
</resources>

